{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Love is sentimental?",
      "category": "love",
      "options": ["true", "maybe", "not sure", "never"],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },

    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "What type of love does God have for us?",
      "category": "love",
      "options": ["Agape", "Romantic", "Friendly", "Family"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },

    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Is romantic love enough for a marriage?",
      "category": "love",
      "options": ["yes", "no", "maybe", "probably"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },

    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "You have to love everyone equally?",
      "category": "love",
      "options": ["Yes", "Not really", "you can't", "maybe"],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },

    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Love grows as you grow in knowledge",
      "category": "love",
      "options": ["True", "False", "usually", "maybe"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },

    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Love can grow by revelation",
      "category": "love",
      "options": ["false", "true", "probably", "maybe"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },

    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "you can grow love by?",
      "category": "love",
      "options": ["actions", "gifts", "money", "sex"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },

    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "you can grow your love in a relationship?",
      "category": "love",
      "options": ["true", "false", "maybe", "probably"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },

    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "You can grow love with all except?",
      "category": "love",
      "options": ["knowledge", "revelation", "actions", "money"],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },

    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "What type of love is the friendship love?",
      "category": "love",
      "options": ["eros", "phlia", "storge", "agape"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },

    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Would you ace this game?",
      "category": "love",
      "options": ["yes", "no", "probably", "on God"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    }
  ]
}
